我們逮到她了
We caught the bitch.
請別傷害我
Please don't hurt me.
不要害怕  女孩
Don't be afraid, girl.
你是誰？
Who are you?
誰來救救我
Somebody please help me.
只有那本邪書能結束這一切
Only the evil book can undo what the evil book has done.
拜託，我只想回家
Please. I just want to go home.
爸爸？
Daddy?
爸爸，你為何這麼做？
Daddy, why are you doing this to me?
他們是誰？
Who are these people?
他們是好人
Look, they are good people.
他們是來幫忙的
They are here to help.
你在說什麼？
What are you talking about?
媽媽呢？
Where's Mom?
媽媽死了，爸爸
Mommy's dead, baby.
你知道的
You know that.
你殺了她
You killed her.
什麼？
What?
真的
You did.
我沒有，你為何這麼說？
No, why are you saying these things?
爸爸  拜託，我只想回家
Daddy, please, I just want to go home.
我只是想回家
I just want to go home.
動手，只有這樣才能拯救她
Do it! It's the only way to save her soul!
我很抱歉，寶貝
I'm so sorry, baby.
爸爸，那是什麼？
Daddy, what is that?
爸爸
Daddy.
爸爸，看著我，是我啊
Daddy, look at me. It's me.
動手，讓你女兒解脫
Do it! Give your daughter peace!
我只想要你抱我，帶我回家
I just want you to hold me and take me home.
求你了！
Please.
拜託住手
Please stop.
我會撕碎你的靈魂
I will rip your soul out, Daddy.
我會吃掉你的靈魂，沒用的東西
I'll rip your soul out, you pathetic fuck!
混賬東西
Motherfucker!
我會殺了你，就像我殺掉…
I will kill you like I killed...
你的婊子
your whore!
干
Fuck!
寶貝，我愛你
I love you, baby.
最近忙什麼，大人物？
How's it going, Mr. Hot Shit City Boy?
- 嘿 ，奧利維亞   - 過來
- Hey, Olivia. - Come here.
用兩手，假裝你很想我
Two arms, please. Like you missed me.
這是我女友 娜塔莉
This is my girl Natalie.
你們車廠之花
Oh, the heartbreaker from your car shop.
你是醫生？
The doctor?
- 事實上她是… - 我是註冊護士
- Actually, she's... - I'm a registered nurse.
護士？
Nurse.
抱歉搞錯
Right, sorry.
你兩小時前就該到了
You were supposed to be here two hours ago, man.
那是萬人迷艾瑞克
And that's our irresistibly charming Eric.
教高中讓你產生負面心態？
Teaching high school finally turned you into a bitter old coot, huh?
不，是你
No, you did.
你讓我們苦等一個早上
You kept us waiting here all morning.
我也很高興見到你，過來
Good to see you, too, man. Come here.
你看起來不錯
You look good.
她在後面等著你
She's waiting for you in the back.
太好了
Great.
嘿  米亞
Hey, Mia.
我不敢相信
I'll be damned.
你真的來了
You actually came.
拜託　我是你哥
Come on, I'm your big brother.
我當然會來
Of course I came.
我知道我看起來很糟
I know I look like road kill.
不　你和以前一樣美
Oh, you look beautiful, as always.
你和以前一樣很會騙人
And you're a charming liar, as always.
爺爺？
Grandpa?
好久不見
Hey, there buddy.
我們最愛這堣F，對嗎？
We always loved this place, didn't we?
它很想你
He missed you a lot, you know.
- 噢  我的天   - 什麼？
- Oh, my God. - What?
- 那是什麼？ - 什麼？
- What is that? - What?
這個，這
Just this, right here. What are you...
這不好玩
It's not funny.
這是鼠李樹做的
This is, uh... It's made from a buckthorn tree.
可以讓你意志堅定
It's supposed to make your will stronger.
我以為你不信這些東西
But I thought you didn't believe in that kind of stuff.
我不信，但你相信，所以也許有用
I don't. But you do, so, well, maybe it'll work.
好吧
Okay.
那我們開始吧
Well, then, let's do this.
答應我　你會陪我到最後
Promise me you'll stay with me until the end.
我哪兒都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你發誓
Cross your heart.
好吧
Okay.
我發誓
Hope to die.
好吧
Okay.
在朋友和家人的見證之下
May my friends and family witness this act,
我真的下定決心要…
an irrevocable promise to my commitment that...
算了
Fuck it.
我發誓不碰這些東西…
I promise not to touch this shit...
再也不碰
ever again.
好了
Okay.
我們來戒毒吧
Let's play cold turkey.
嗯
Well...
我知道有些毒蟲今晚要開派對
I know some slugs are gonna have a party tonight.
大衛…
David...
米亞將要經歷她生命中最糟糕的三天
Mia's about to go through the worst three days of her life.
懂嗎？戒斷反應會讓她經歷極度的身體疼痛
Okay? Withdrawal's gonna make her experience extreme body pain,
嘔吐，冷顫，妄想癥…
vomiting, chills, paranoia...
這一點也不好
It's not gonna be nice.
為啥是三天？
Why three days?
因為三天之後…
Because after three days...
疼痛就消失了
the pain subsides.
她就會永遠擺脫麻煩
And she'll be off the hook for good.
米亞是很堅強的 她會沒事的
Mia's a strong girl. She'll be okay.
嗯
Yeah.
希望這還能用
Hopefully, this still works.
等一下
Wait.
好像有人進來過
Looks like someone broke in.
小心點
Be careful.
那是什麼味道？
What is that smell?
可能是年輕人來這媔摯s作樂
Some teenagers probably just broke in here to drink beer and bump uglies.
沒錯
Exactly.
媽媽要是看到一定氣壞了
Mom would have hated seeing the cabin like this.
好吧
Okay.
我們來整理一下
Let's make this place livable.
不 用我的相機
No, use my camera.
好吧 好吧
Fine, fine.
你還好嗎？
Are you okay?
你記得媽媽唱的搖籃曲嗎？
Do you remember that lullaby Mom used to sing us?
歌詞好像是…
It was something like...
「我的寶貝，該說再見了」
"Baby, little baby, it's time to say goodbye.
「我的寶貝…」
"Baby, little baby..."
米亞，你現在不該想悲傷的回憶
Mia, please, I don't think you need sad memories in your head right now.
媽咪不是悲傷的回憶
Mom is not a sad one.
你知道我的意思
You know what I mean.
你知道嗎？她在醫院臨死前
You know what? Her final days at the hospital...
媽媽常以為我是你
Mom sometimes thought I was you.
有一次她一整天都叫我大衛
She even called me David for a whole day, once.
我順著他，因為…
And I played along, 'cause...
米亞，我也想去陪她，真的
Mia, look, I wanted to be there. Okay? I did.
但媽病情惡化時
But by the time Mom got bad,
我才剛找到芝加哥修車廠的工作
I had just gotten the job at the garage in Chicago.
我當時真的走不開
I don't know, I had a hard time finding the right moment to come back.
結果媽媽就過世了，所以…
And then it was too late. So...
也許你很幸運
Maybe you were lucky,
不用看到媽媽那樣
not to see her the way that I did.
她看起來還好
It looks like she's doing okay.
大衛，我有事要跟你說
David, there's something you need to know.
好吧
Okay.
我們去年夏天就做過一次
We already tried this whole thing back in Flint last summer.
米亞那時也發誓
Mia made the same promises.
她…
She...
同樣戲劇性地發誓要保持清醒
took the same dramatic vow of sobriety
然後把毒品丟掉
before chucking her dope down the toilet.
她戒了8小時然後放棄
She lasted eight hours and quit.
所以這次不能再給她機會
So, we don't want to give her that chance this time.
什麼意思？
What do you mean?
大衛，等她崩潰時…
David, when she breaks,
相信我，她會的
and believe me, she will,
我們不能讓她離開
we don't want to let her leave.
你要強迫她留在這堙H
What do you mean? You want force her to stay here?
米亞？
Mia?
這次只能來硬的
This time the only way is the hard way, man.
她經不起再次吸毒過量
She won't survive another OD.
什麼？
What?
米亞吸毒過量？
Mia OD'd?
不光吸毒過量
She didn't just OD.
按規定來說，你妹死了
Legally, your sister died.
醫生給她電擊才救活她
They had to defibrillate her.
天哪
Jesus.
我們的態度必須一致，不然沒用
Look, we all need to be together on this. Otherwise it won't work.
乖狗狗
Good boy.
我是來和我妹妹重修舊好的
I came here to make things better with my sister, not worse.
若她要我…
If she asks me to...
帶他回家，我會這麼做
take her home at some point, I'm gonna have to do it.
我受不了了！該死
I can't stand it! Fuck!
- 我受不了了  - 味道？什麼味道？
- I can't stand it! - Smell? What smell?
那是什麼鬼味道？
What the fuck is that smell?
我知道
I know, I know.
沒事的
It's okay. It's okay.
我再也受不了那個味道
I can't stand that fucking smell anymore.
躺下，好嗎？
Lie down, okay?
我們都在這堻郁A
We're all here for you. I know, I know.
我們都在這
We're all here.
我們不會離開
We're not going anywhere.
戒斷癥狀開始發作了
Withdrawal's kicking in hard.
這應該可以幫你度過今晚
This should help you get through the night.
不知道你們是怎麼回事
I don't know what is wrong with you people,
怎麼受得了那股屍臭味
but there is something dead and it reeks.
我沒聞到
But there is no smell.
你現在只是過度敏感
You're just extra-sensitive right now.
我受不了那個味道
I just can't stand that fucking smell anymore.
等一下
Wait.
那是血嗎？
Oh, is that blood?
該死
Oh, shit.
你還認為是我太敏感？
What's your medical diagnosis now?
真的好臭
It fucking stinks.
該死，小心
Shit. Careful.
樓梯都腐爛了
These steps are old and rotten.
就像這間房子一樣
Yeah, like this whole freaking house.
我知道
I know.
聞起來像頭髮燒焦
It smells like burnt hair.
好像是那後面
I think it's back there.
我的天
Oh, my God!
該死
Shit.
這是什麼？
What is this?
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
巫術？
Witchcraft?
誰會做這種事？
Who would do this?
有人在這媬N東西
Shit, something burned here.
你看
Look.
可惡
Shit, man.
這堨L媽發生了什麼？
What the fuck happened here?
我們不要過度反應，好嗎？
Let's not go crazy over this. Okay?
我等下會把死貓移走
I'll bury those dead cats out back later.
那些味道很快就會消失
Yeah. The smell will be gone in no time.
最好是
Yeah, okay.
那些巫毒的鬼玩意兒怎麼辦？
And what about the voodoo shit they did down there, huh?
不，巫毒用的是人偶那些東西
No, no, no. Voodoo is more about dolls and personal artifacts.
- 這不一樣了 - 艾瑞克，別說了
- This is something different. - Eric, that's enough.
你們不該碰那地下室的東西
You shouldn't have touched anything from that basement.
「納塔隆迪蒙多」
Naturom Demonic
「康達」
"Kunda."
「阿斯特塔」
"Astratta."
「蒙托賽」
"Montosse."
「康達」
"Canda."
老天，饒了我吧
Please, God, give me a break.
米亞
Mia.
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
抱歉，我現在必須離開這
I'm sorry, but I have to get out of here right now.
別鬧了，睡衣派對還沒結束
No, come on. The slumber party isn't over yet.
我們還沒玩「大風吹」，是嗎？
Yeah, we still haven't played "Fuck, Marry, Kill," right?
米亞，聽著
Mia, please look... Mia...
我快發瘋了
I'm going insane here.
奧利維亞  我覺得我快瘋了
Olivia, I feel like I'm losing my mind.
怎麼了？
Mia, what is it?
我這次真的會戒　好嗎？
I will go through with this, okay?
我只是…不能在這塈
I just... I can't do it here.
米亞
Mia...
我們說好不讓你回去
We've decided we're not gonna take you back.
我們不能再失去你
We can't lose you again.
你這次必須撐到最後
You're gonna have to stick it out this time.
大衛，載我回去
David, drive me home.
快點，大衛
Come on, David.
米亞 也許他們是對的
Mia, maybe they're right.
你應該支持我，不是他們
You were supposed to be here to support me, not them.
- 我是在支持你 米亞 所以我才來這 - 天哪
- I'm here for you, Mia. That's why I came. - Oh, my God.
我真是白癡
I'm such an idiot.
竟然笨到以為這次…
To think for once in my life,
我能依靠你
I could count on you.
米亞，我們只是想試著幫助你
Mia, we're just trying to help you.
不用了
Yeah, well, fuck you very much!
艾瑞克，讓她靜一靜
Eric, leave her alone.
米亞
Mia.
Mia!
太好了
Perfect.
干…
Fuck this. Fuck, fuck.
我到底在幹嘛？
What the fuck am I doing?
米亞
Mia!
- 米亞 - 米亞
- Mia! - Mia!
米亞
Mia.
Mia!
米亞
Mia.
Mia!
米亞
- 米亞  - 該死
- Mia! - Shit.
天哪
Oh, my God.
她怎麼樣了？
Hey, how's she doing?
她說樹林埵陪茪k的
Um, she's talking about a woman in the woods.
還說那些樹攻擊她
How the forest attacked her.
我不知道，應該只是戒斷癥狀
I don't know. It's just crazy withdrawal talk.
也許我們該帶她去醫院？
Well, don't you think we should take her to a hospital?
我也覺得情況有些失控
I feel like we're in over our heads here.
好
Okay.
我給她的治療和醫院一樣
I am giving her the exact same treatment she would get at a hospital.
若現在離開，一切都沒意義了
If we leave now, all of this mess will have been for nothing.
她手上的傷怎麼來的？
Okay. What about the wounds on her arms?
我拔出一些刺
I pulled some thorns out.
她應該是跑進有刺的樹林
It looks like she might've run into a thorn bush out there.
她可能是故意的
She probably did it on purpose.
什麼？
What?
大衛
David,
現在開始，她會想盡辦法離開
from now on, she is gonna do whatever it takes to get out of here.
米亞
Mia.
你該把衣服換掉
Listen, you've gotta get out of those clothes.
- 好嗎？去洗個澡   - 大衛
- All right? Take a shower. - David.
拜託
Please.
求求你
你必須帶我…
You have to get me...
離開這
...out of here.
沒人說戒毒很簡單
Mia, look, nobody said this was gonna be easy.
不
No.
你不瞭解
You don't understand.
大衛，樹林埵釭F西
There was something in the woods, David.
我覺得那東西…
And I think it's in here...
現在就在屋子
with us now.
在這屋堙H
With me in the room?
聽著，這只是你的幻覺
Look, you know it's all in your head.
試著撐過今晚
Just try to get it together.
明天就會好多了，好嗎？
You'll feel better tomorrow, okay?
你會感謝我們
You'll be glad we were such assholes.
好吧
Okay.
艾瑞克，你在幹什麼？
Eric, what are you doing?
不要在看那本書好嗎？
Please, would you just get rid of that thing?
你應該去地下室幫你朋友清理
You should be downstairs helping your friend clean up that mess.
我不知道你在說誰？
I don't know who you're talking about.
少假裝你不開心他
Come on. Don't act like you don't care about him.
我知道你關心
I know you do.
誰叫他過去幾年都不理我們
Well, I think we can all agree he hasn't cared about us for the past freaking century.
至少他來了
Well, he's here now.
是啊
Yeah.
真不可思議
Truly amazing.
爺爺？
Grandpa?
Grandpa!
爺爺？
Grandpa?
過來，狗狗
Come here, boy.
操
Fuck.
爺爺
Grandpa.
不  不  不
No,no,no.
狗狗，過來
Hey, boy. Come here.
怎麼回事？
What did you get into?
可惡
Fuck.
發生了什麼事？
What happened?
米亞？
Mia?
她在洗澡
She's in the shower.
發生了什麼事？大衛？
What happened? David?
米亞？
Mia?
米亞　開門
Mia, open the door.
米亞  開門
Hey, Mia, open the door.
米亞  開門！
Mia, open the door!
大衛  你在幹嘛？
David, what are you doing?
大衛，告訴我怎麼回事
David, stop, tell me what's going on.
米亞  把門打開！
Mia! Mia, open the fucking door!
米亞
Mia?
米亞  把門打開！
Mia, open the fucking door!
大衛！
David!
住手！
Stop it!
米亞
Mia!
米亞？
Mia?
奧利維亞
Olivia!
天哪
Holy shit!
米亞
Mia!
可惡
Shit.
太誇張了
This is insane.
可惡，在哪堙H
Fuck. Where is it?
怎麼可能
This can't be happening.
我 ..嗯... 我 ..
I, um... I...
我給她打針讓她睡一、兩小時
I gave her a sedative. So, she should be out for a couple of hours.
他傷勢嚴重，大概…
But, fuck, her burns are serious. Like,
二、三級灼傷
second, third degree.
這不該發生
This is so wrong.
誰知道她會做這種事
Well, nobody could have known she would do something so twisted!
不  你應該知道
No, you should have known!
我們到這兒後都聽你的指示
We've all been following your lead since we got here.
米亞要走時　我們就該離開的
We should have left when Mia wanted to.
寶貝，別這樣，我們不要慌
Baby, please! Okay? Let's not lose our heads, okay?
幸運的話，雨再幾小時就會停
Look, with any luck, it'll stop raining in a couple of hours,
明天早上就能過河
and we'll be able to cross the creek in the morning,
帶她去醫院
and we'll take her to a hospital.
好嗎？一切都會沒事
Okay? Everything's gonna be fine.
「一切都會沒事」？
"Everything's gonna be fine?"
一切都會沒事
Everything's gonna be fine.
你大概沒注意到每件事都不對勁
I don't know if you've noticed this, but nothing has been fine.
而且每況愈下，越來越糟
And everything's been getting worse every second.
米亞？
Mia?
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
米亞  把槍放下
Mia, put the gun down.
拜託把槍放下
Put the gun down, please.
米亞
Mia.
把那該死的槍放下
Put the fucking gun down!
去死吧
Die!
我會把你們一個一個解決
One by one, we will take you!
你們今晚都要受死
You are all going to die tonight.
去拿槍，快
The gun. The gun, quick!
寶貝？
Baby?
米亞？
Mia!
放我出去！
- 讓我出去！ - 她真的瘋了
- Let me out! - She's totally psychotic.
我的天，她眼睛怎麼了？
Oh, my God, what happened to her eyes?
她在做什麼？
What's she doing?
聽起來像在撞東西
it sounds like she's hitting herself against something.
不可能
This is impossible.
我給她的劑量能讓馬睡著
I just gave her enough sedative to put a horse to sleep.
再給她一針
Give her another shot!
那會讓她陷入昏迷
That could put her into a coma.
她就快撞死自己了
For Christ's sakes, Olivia, she's gonna kill herself down there!
快去拿藥
Go get the shot!
我必須把彈殼取出來
I gotta get the shrapnel out of my arm.
我包埵酗p夾子
What? I have tweezers in my purse.
大衛  聽我說
David. Listen to me.
我覺得給她鎮定劑沒用
I don't think a tranquilizer's gonna do shit.
因為我們不是在處理恐慌癥
'Cause I don't think we're dealing with a freaking panic attack here!
我覺得米亞會這樣
I'm scared that what's happening to Mia has something to do
和地下室的東西有關
with the fucking witchcraft in the basement!
奧利維亞
Olivia!
奧利維亞？
Olivia?
你還好嗎？
Are you okay?
奧利維亞？
Olivia?
奧利維亞，你在堶捧F嘛？
Olivia, what are you doing in there?
奧利維亞
Olivia.
奧利維亞？
你還好嗎？
Are you okay?
天哪
Oh, my God!
你幹嘛這樣？
Why the fuck did you do that?
殺了他
Kill him.
不
No!
她想殺我
She tried to kill me.
可惡
Fuck.
壓好，可以嗎？
You hold that. You got it?
壓住這
Hold it there, okay? Hold it there. Hold...
可惡
Fuck it.
大衛
David,
我做了很糟的事
I did something terrible.
我相信你不是故意的
I'm sure you didn't mean to hurt her.
我殺的東西不是奧利維亞
That thing I killed was not Olivia.
他失血過多
He's losing too much blood.
寶貝　他需要水和糖
Baby, he needs water and sugar. Okay?
去啊
Go.
快去
Go!
好 好
Okay. Okay.
- 好了  - 大衛
- All right. - David.
我念了那本書上的字
I read a passage from that book.
這是… 這是某種禱告
It was... It was some sort of prayer.
我釋放了某些東西
I released something, David.
我釋放了邪惡的東西
I released something evil.
娜塔莉？
Natalie?
米亞嗎？
Mia?
娜塔莉
Natalie.
我為何在地下室？
What am I doing down here?
我的腳好痛
My leg hurts.
我不能動
I can't move.
我要下來了，好嗎？
I'm gonna come down there, okay?
你們為何把我鎖在這堙H
Why did you lock me down here?
你們應該幫我才對
You were supposed to help me.
我們是在試著幫你
Hey, we're trying to help you, okay?
你失控了，你知道嗎？
You were out of control, you know?
你變得很暴力，我們不知如何是好
You got violent and we didn't know what else to do.
米亞，剛發生很恐怖的事
Mia, look, something really terrible has happened
我們必須離開這
and we have to get out of here now. Okay?
你不懂
You don't understand.
他不會讓你離開
He's not gonna let you leave!
除非他得到你
And he's not gonna stop till he has you.
除非他得到所有人
Until he has all of you!
拜託…
Please...
我聞得到你骯髒的靈魂
I can smell your filthy soul.
親我，你這賤貨
Kiss me, you dirty cunt!
帥哥，下來讓我吸你的屌
Why don't you come down here, so I can suck your cock, pretty boy!
米亞
Mia.
米亞不在這堙A你這白癡
Mia's not here, you fucking idiot!
你妹妹正在地獄被強姦
Your little sister is being raped in hell!
家 我要回家
Home. I want to go home.
謝謝你的水
Thanks for the water.
艾瑞克
Eric.
我以為這樣可以結束一切
I don't know why, but I thought this would end it.
但這本書燒不起來
But this book does not burn.
它燒不起來
It does not fucking burn.
告訴我怎麼回事
Tell me what's going on here.
這本書是用….
This book uses some
（你將受苦）
ancient alphabet.
堶惘酗@些翻譯，但…
There's some translations, but...
很零星
Just scattered notes.
它們全都指向…
They all refer to some...
一種邪惡的東西
Evil entity.
奪取靈魂的…
A taker of souls.
惡魔
A demon.
上面說…
It says...
「等他吞噬五條靈魂」
"Once he feasts on five souls,
「天空會再下血，惡魔…」
"the sky will bleed again and the abomination
「會從地域升起」
"will rise from Hell."
太荒唐了
This is insane.
這東西…
This thing...
像水蛭緊附在米亞的靈魂
is attached to Mia's soul like a leech.
它變成她
It's becoming her.
若要停止一切
If we want to stop this,
若要救米亞…
if we want to help Mia...
我想我們必須殺了她
I think we're gonna have to kill her.
你說什麼？
What did you say?
上面寫…
Everything says...
艾瑞克，我們不要殺人
Eric! We're not gonna fucking kill anybody!
你有沒有聽到自己說的話？
Are you listening to yourself?
也許是地下室那些死貓
What about those dead cats down in the basement?
也許它們有病毒
I mean, maybe they had some disease.
害米亞感染
I mean, some virus that... It spread to Mia,
然後她吐的時候又傳染給奧利維亞
and then she passed it to Olivia when she puked all over her face!
那種病毒…
But what kind of a virus...
會讓人拿玻璃割自己的臉？
makes a person cut off their face with a piece of glass?
天哪
Oh, God. Oh, God.
我不知道我們面對的是什麼
I don't know what we're dealing with here, okay?
但等雨一停
But it stopped raining,
等幾個小時 水位就會下降
and in a couple of hours, the river will be clear,
我們就能離開這
and we're gonna get out of this place.
我們所有人
All of us.
到哪堥瓣ㄜ垠n
It doesn't matter where we go.
若現在不採取行動
If we don't do something right now,
到時候我們都會死
we're all gonna be dead by then!
還給我…
Give me back...
我的手
my hand.
我們要來抓你了
We're gonna get you
別再偷看了
Not another peep
該睡覺了
Time to go to sleep
睡吧
Sleep.
睡吧 睡吧
Sleep. Sleep.
住手，賤人，不准割
Don't do it, you little bitch! Don't cut it off!
不准割
Don't cut it off!
去你的
FUCK you!
不…
No, no, no, no, no...
不 不！
No, no, no...
我必須要做 而且現在我感覺好多了
I had to do it. And I feel much better now.
等等，寶貝，請等一下
Hold on, baby. Hold on, please.
艾瑞克和我打算阻止這一切，好嗎？
Eric and I are gonna put a stop to this, okay?
我保證一切都會沒事
I promise that everything's gonna be fine.
好嗎，寶貝？
Okay? Okay, baby?
她把她的手切掉
She just cut her fucking arm off.
這樣叫沒事？
Does that sound fine?
這些文字混亂
These inscriptions are confusing,
有時相互矛盾
sometimes contradictory,
但有件事是一致的
but they're consistent about one thing.
要停止這一切
In order to stop this,
必須淨化被附身者
the possessed must be cleansed.
要淨化
Purified.
這本書提到三個方法
The book describes three specific ways.
活埋
A live burial.
肢解
Bodily dismemberment.
還有火燒淨化
And purification by fire.
你確定這有用嗎？
Are you sure this will work?
如果我們…
If we...
殺了我妹妹，她就會得到安息？
If I kill my sister, she'll be at peace?
我確定嗎？當然不
Am I... Am I sure? Of course not.
這又不是科學實驗
This is not a science book!
但我能確定一件事
But look, I'm sure of one thing.
米亞體內的東西…
Whatever is inside Mia...
就是這一切的根源
is the cause of all this.
她死了
If she dies,
那東西才會死
then this thing is gonna die with her.
要是她只是瘋了呢？
What if she just lost her mind?
也許她只是需要看醫生？
What if she just needs a doctor?
什麼？醫生？
What? A doctor?
我媽媽死在精神病院，她瘋了
My mom died in a mental hospital. She was crazy.
她喪失心智，成了野獸
She was deranged, she was a monster.
我一直很怕米亞和我會像她一樣
I've always feared that me and Mia would end up like her.
那好吧，米亞已經瘋了
So... Okay, so Mia went crazy.
那奧利維亞呢？娜塔莉呢？
Okay. What about Olivia? What about Natalie?
也許我們都瘋了
Maybe we've all gone crazy.
你只是個膽小鬼
You're just a fucking coward.
你知道我們該怎麼做
You know exactly what we have to do,
但你害怕到不敢去做
but you're too scared to go through with it.
我要放火把這媬N了
I'm gonna burn this fucking place down.
好結束這場惡夢
And I'm gonna end this nightmare.
你乾脆逃走好了
Why don't you just run away?
去找個地方躲起來
Go hide beneath some rock somewhere.
這你最在行了
You know you're great at that.
可惡
Oh, shit.
她跑哪去了？
Where the fuck did she go?
大衛
David.
先去拿那把槍
Take it before she does.
想玩嗎 小不點？
Want to play, little man?
不
No!
站住
Stop!
不…
No,no,no!
不  不  不！
No, no, no...
大衛
David.
你為什麼要傷害我？
Why are you hurting me?
我的臉好痛
My face hurts.
為什麼？
Why?
為什麼我的臉好痛？
Why... Why does my face hurt?
寶貝
Baby.
小娜
Nat.
撐著點，到了
Come on. Come on, man. Here we are.
撐著點
Hey, hey, hey. Hold on.
不要死，拜託
Don't die on me, please!
現在死掉也不錯
Dying wouldn't be so bad right now.
我不想被惡魔附身
I just don't want to become the devil's bitch.
我會做我該做的事
I'm gonna do what I gotta do.
我會做該做的事，好嗎？
I'm gonna do what I gotta do. Okay?
抱歉，米亞
I'm sorry, Mia.
我愛你
I love you.
「我的寶貝」
Baby, little baby
「該說再見了」
It's time to say goodbye
「我的寶貝」
Baby, little baby
「我每天都會想你」
I'll miss you day and night
「我的寶貝」
Baby, my sweet baby
「我每天都會寫信給你」
I'll write you every day
「寶貝，別哭」
Baby, don't cry, baby
「我希望我能留下「
I wish that I could stay
我下不了手
I can't do this.
我沒辦法
這次只能來硬的
This time, the only fucking way is the hard way!
大衛
David.
兇手
Murderer.
懦夫
Coward.
艾瑞克
Eric.
嘿  你還好嗎？
大衛
David.
我很想你  夥計
I missed you, man.
你知道的，兄弟
You know that, buddy.
大衛？
David?
我動不了，我不能呼吸
I can't move! I can't breathe!
大衛
David!
救我
Help me!
大衛，救我
Help me, David!
你不是她
You're not her.
大衛！
David!
救我
Help me!
你不是她！
You're not her!
你為什麼恨我，大衛？
Why do you hate me, David?
我知道你恨我
I know you do.
你離開家
You left home.
把媽媽丟給我一個人
You left me all alone with our sick mother.
而我只是一個孩子
And I was just a kid.
你害我撒謊
You made me lie.
每次她尖叫你的名字
Every time she screamed your name,
我只能騙她說你在路上了
I told her you were coming to see her.
就像你答應的
Like you promised.
但你從沒回來過
But you never did.
拜託別說了，我求你
Please stop it, I'm begging you.
我知道現在媽媽恨你
I know Mother hates you now,
她在地獄等你
and she waits for you in hell.
閉嘴
Shut up.
你會燒死的，大衛
You will burn, David.
你會和你那吸毒的妹妹一起燒死在地獄
You will burn in hell alongside your junkie sister.
閉嘴
Shut up.
你想殺我，就會被燒死在地獄，你這個混蛋！
You're gonna burn in hell for trying to kill me, you motherfucker!
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我應該回家的
I should have been there.
我應該回家陪你的
I should've been there for you.
拜託回來
Come on. Please, come back.
快 快 快
Come on, come on, come on.
米亞，快回來
Come on, Mia. Come back to me. Come on, please.
你安息吧
Okay, you are at peace.
你現在是在和平
You're at peace now.
大衛？
David?
米亞？
Mia?
好可怕
it was so horrible.
真的好可怕
It was so horrible.
好了，沒事了
It's okay. It's all over now.
謝謝你沒離開我
Thanks for not leaving me, David.
在這媯央A我去拿車鑰匙
Wait here. I'm gonna get the car keys.
- 好嗎？ - 好
- Okay? - Yeah.
大衛
David!
- 走，快走  - 不 不
- Go. Please, go. - No, no, no.
去！
Go!
我不要走，我不走
I'm not gonna go anywhere. I'm not going anywhere.
鑰匙拿著，我們走
Mia, take the keys. Look at me, let's go.
快點，我們走
Come on. Come on, let's go.
快走
Get out of here.
不
No! No!
大衛
David!
不 不
No! No!
大衛 大衛
David! David!
他要來了
He's coming.
米亞
Mia.
過來，賤人
Come here, you bitch!
快點
Come on.
你會死在這，沒用的毒蟲
You're gonna die here, you pathetic junkie!
我受夠了
I've had enough of this shit.
我要吃掉你的靈魂
I will feast on your soul.
吃這個，王八蛋
Feast on this, motherfucker!
去死吧！
Die!
回到地獄吧，婊子！
Go back to Hell, bitch.
你還好嗎 孩子？
Are you okay, kiddo?
救救我
Help me.
全能的上帝
God Almighty.
別擔心，孩子
Don't you worry, kid.
我帶你去醫院，你會很快得到救治
I'm taking you to the hospital, and they'll patch you up in no time.
你會恢復健康的
You'll be right as rain.
我確信在康達堥廢墟有了驚人發現
I believe I have made a significant find in the Candarian Ruins...
有一本關於古蘇美人喪葬的書
A volume of ancient Sumerian burial practices and funerary incantations.
書名"納塔隆迪蒙多"
It is entitled "Naturom Demonto."
意思是"死亡之書"
Roughly translated, "Book of the Dead."
這本書用人皮作封面
The book is bound in human flesh
用人血書寫
and inked in human blood.
是關於惡魔復活
It deals with demons, demon resurrection,
在森林遊蕩的黑暗勢力
those forces which roam the forest and dark bowers of man's domain.
前幾頁警告說這些不朽的生物…
The first few pages warn that these enduring creatures
看起來死了 但絕不會死
may lie dormant, but are never truly dead.
這本書上的咒語可讓他們復活
They may be recalled to active life through the incantations presented in this book.
只要唸咒語就給了惡魔通行證
It is through recitation of these passages
來奪取人的靈魂
that the demons are given license to possess the living.
我看到黑影在森林堬劓
I have seen the dark shadows moving in the woods,
我相信被我召喚出的東西
and I have no doubt that whatever I have resurrected through this book
已經來找我了
is sure to come calling for me.
酷啊
Groovy.